Dare to enter the secretive world of a sexy young spy-trainee.
Secret Weapons is a drama, tv movie film directed by Don Taylor.
Soviet High School girls are sent to the U.S.
where they are taught to become secret agents and use sex to find information.
Vera Malevich, played by Sally Kellerman.
Elena Koslov, played by Linda Hamilton.
Jack Spaulding, played by Hunt Block.
Aunt Rosa Koslov, played by Viveca Lindfors.
Tamara / Becky, played by Geena Davis.
General Suslev, played by Barrie Ingham.
Sherlock Holmes and the Secret Weapon (1942) is the fourth in the Basil Rathbone/Nigel Bruce series of 14 Sherlock
Holmes films which updated the characters created by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle to the then present day.
The film is credited as an adaptation of Conan Doyle's 1903 short story "The Adventure of the
Dancing Men," though the only element from the source material is the dancing men code.
Rather, it is a spy film taking place on the background of the then
ongoing Second World War with an original premise.
The film concerns the kidnapping of a Swiss scientist by their nemesis Professor
Moriarty, to steal a new bomb sight and sell it to Nazi Germany.
Sherlock Holmes and Dr.
John Watson have to crack a secret code in order to save the country.
The film is one of four films in the series which are in the public domain.
The film explores themes of spy, blackmail, love, surveillance.
The tone is emotional.